Kanishak

Kanishak1998@icloud.com

9779610365

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kanishaksh

SUMMARY:

My name is Kanishak. I am from Ludhiana, Punjab. I am 25 years old and I have completed my MBA in Marketing from Chitkara University, Punjab. Currently, I am working as an Assistant Manager-Client Relations at OFB Tech Pvt Itd in Ludhiana, Punjab. Earlier I have worked as a Client Service Executive at Indiamart and Business Development Executive at Sage IT Inc in Mohali, Punjab. I have strong passion for marketing management and currently looking for a job in the same. I am certified in Brand Management from University of London and also certified in Digital Marketing from Google Digital Garage.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:

EXAM/DEGREE	SESSION	NAME OF INSTITUTE	UNIVERSITY/BOARD	PERCENTAGE
MBA Marketing	2021-2023	Chitkara Business School	Chitkara University, Punjab	9.28 CGPA
Bachelor of Arts	2017-2020	SCD Government College, Ludhiana	Panjab University, Chandigarh	72%
Class XII	2015-2017	BVM Sr. Sec. School, Kitchlu Naga, Ludhiana	CBSE	78.40 %
Class X	2013-2014	BVM Sr. Sec. School, Kitchlu Naga, Ludhiana	CBSE	8.6 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE:

OFB Tech Pvt Ltd, Ludhiana Assistant Manager-Client Relations

April 2024 - Present

Responsibilities:

- Managing the purchase and sales of Wire rods in entire North India.
- Traveling all over north India to find potential customers of Wire Rods.
- Assist in developing sales strategies to achieve targets and maximize revenue from wire rod sales.
- Build and maintain strong relationships with existing and potential customers to understand their needs and provide suitable solutions.
- Oversee the processing of customer orders, ensuring accuracy, timeliness, and adherence to company policies and procedures.
- Negotiate pricing agreements with customers to achieve optimal profitability while remaining competitive in the market.
- Prepare regular sales reports, including sales performance, market trends, and customer feedback, for management review.
- Address customer inquiries, complaints, and issues in a timely and satisfactory manner, striving to maintain high levels of customer satisfaction.
- Assess and mitigate risks related to credit, market dynamics, and other factors that may impact wire rod sales performance.

IndiaMart, Ludhiana Client Service Executive Responsibilities:

July 2023 - Present

- Having client base of more than 125 companies.
- Increase in company's revenue of almost ₹28Lakhs in total time frame of working.
- To provide best possible service to clients.
- To penetrate all targeted accounts and originate selling opportunities for the company products and services.
- To set up and deliver sales presentations, product/service demonstrations on a daily basis.
- Responsible for client retention, per client revenue optimization & renewals.
- To ensure systematic follow-up with the client organizations to take the sales pitch to time-bound closure.
- To be an interface between the customer and internal support teams to ensure that the customer receives the best possible service from the company.
- To ensure that all payments are collected as per the company payment terms.
- Ensure adherence to sales processes and requirements.
- Achievement of monthly, quarterly & yearly business plan.

Sage IT Inc., Mohali Business Development Executive Responsibilities:

- Understand the requirements of a position as provided by the client and served the requirements based on skillset, experience, and duration of project, hourly rates of salary, communication skills and also other aspects to serve the requirement.
- Generating leads through cold calling, networking and referrals.
- Managing a balanced sales funnel, executing all steps of the sales process from target to close to continually secure new business.
- Research, collect and maintain data through Zoom info.
- Maintaining and growing a client account base.
- Exceed all standards for prospecting calls, presentations, proposals and closes.
- Ensure a high level of customer satisfaction maintaining close contact with all customers including follow up on concerns or other issues
- Provide a solution-based sales approach to drive new business with high end premium customers with highvalue products
- Negotiate contracts and rate agreements
- Develop, execute and monitor strategic and tactical goals to maximize sales, profit and to ensure sales targets are met or exceeded
- Provide documented activity reports of sales efforts on a daily, weekly and monthly basis
- Provide ongoing reporting and analysis, including: territory trending, sales reports/analysis, CRM reports, trade spending analysis, expense reports, etc.
- Follow all company policies, ethics and company procedures

TalentServe. Remote

May 2022- July 2022

Marketing Intern- Marketing & Business Development Manager Responsibilities:

- Maintain working relationships with clients.
- Lead generation for the company and then converting those leads into sales.
- Understanding and Reaching prospects with right deals at right time.
- Increasing Brand awareness.
- Research and Development.
- Increase in user base of the company
- Social Media marketing

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Brand Management: Aligning Business, Brand and Behaviour University of London
- Understanding Business in China University of Nottingham Ningbo, China
- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google Digital Garage
- Strategy Consulting- Boston Consulting Group (BCG)
- Use Canva to Create Social Media Visuals for Business Coursera
- Create a Business Marketing Brand Kit Using Canva Coursera
- Search Engine Optimization on Squarespace- Coursera

SKILLS:

- Digital Marketing
- Google SEO
- SEM
- Email Marketing
- Logo designing
- Image and Video Editing
- Good analytics skills
- Communication skills
- Brand Management
- Leadership
- Public Speaking
- Problem Solving
- Public Relations
- Graphic Designing

CO-CURRICULAR & EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACHIEVEMENTS:

- Bronze medallist Inter-university wrestling
- Wrestling 4x Gold medal at Zonal level wrestling 2x Silver medal at district level wrestling
- Kabaddi- Silver medal at Sahodaya level (North zone) Captain of Kabaddi team of BVM Kitchlu Nagar, Ludhiana.